so let's see if we can compute the size
of the flat page table let's say that
our page table needs to have eight bytes
per entry for example because it has a
64-bit physical address space let's say
that the page size is 4 kilobytes let's
say that the system only has 2 processes
that are active let's say that the
system only really has 2 gigabytes of
physical memory let's say that the
programs are creating 32-bit virtual
addresses let's say that the process
number 1 is using only 1 megabyte of its
available 32-bit address space and let's
say that the process number 2 is using a
gigabyte of its virtual memory it could
use up to 4 gigabytes but it's only
using 1 gigabyte the question for you is
what is the total size of all the page
tables in the system in megabytes